Godwin Odafe Otokina

Lagos, Nigeria. (234) 8136293752

otokinaodafe@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-otokina-631775161/

https://godwinotokina.com

I am a Passionate and Highly Competent software developer with about 4 years experience in planning, developing, deploying and maintaining Full Stack Web Applications. I have a firm grasp of the Entire Life Cycle of Software Development (SDLC). And I currently Lead a small team where we build new features, update and maintain a fintech application processing thousands of transactions daily.

Skills and Technologies

Skills: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, PHP, C#.

Technologies: React, Vue, Node, Express, Typescript, Bootstrap, Tailwind Css, Jest, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Jest, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Jest, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Jest, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Jest, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Tailwind Css, Mocha, Git, Docker, Jira, Trello, Mongo DB, Mocha, Git, Docker, Mocha, Git, Gocha, Gocha, Gocha, Git, Gocha, Go

PostgreSql, MySql, Firebase and FireStore, Linux Server Administration (Linode).

Want to Learn: Aws, Serverless, Go Lang.

Experience

MARCH 2021 - PRESENT

Itex Integrated Services, Lagos, Nigeria - Team Lead, Vas Applications - iisysgroup.com

- Lead the Full Stack development Team of Itex Value Added Services.
- Plan, Code and Execute New Features of the Vas System, Code Reviews, Server Administrators .
- Revamped various integrations to increase transaction speed and reduce failures, thus increasing success rate to about 95%.

MARCH 2020 - FEB 2021

Itex Integrated Services, Lagos, Nigeria - Software Developer - iisysgroup.com

- Co Developed the Itex Value Added Services Version 4.0.
- Interpret UI designs to Implement an Agent Onboarding system (https://www.payvice.com/vice/agents/onboard)

JUNE 2019 - FEB 2020

Bloverse, Lagos Nigeria - Full Stack Developer - bloverse.com

- Build new UI components in Vue.js for the Bloverse Web Application and Bloverse PWA
- Interpret UI designs to code the Bloverse Web app and Bloverse PWA.
- Modify Existing and Create new Api Endpoints in Node.js using Test Driven Development Approach.

DEC 2018 - JUNE 2019

Ikooba Technologies, Lagos Nigeria - Software Developer

- Build new Features to Improve the performance of Bmac Ims and Bmac Accounting softwares. https://onebmac.com/
- Build the Bmac Fixed assets Registrar Module in Laravel and Vue.js.

Education

NOV 2011 - SEPT 2015

UNIVERSITY OF BENIN, Benin City, Nigeria - Bsc. Chemistry

Other Projects

Afrimart: http://afrimartone.com/

Afrimart is an Ecommerce platform that connects the African market to the World.

Role: Frontend Developer

Tech Stack: React

One Port 365: https://app.oneport365.com

One port is a shipping management Platform that covers the entire Import and Export Process for goods and services

Role: Full Stack Developer **Tech Stack**: React and Node.js